Do Thien Y

Software Engineer

700000, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam Vietnam



+4 Years of Experiences in software engineering, specialized in JavaScript/TypeScript Stacks and proficient in web development. Looking forward to a brighter future in tech.

Web Development Proficient (+4 yoe)	Frameworks Good (+4 yoe)	Programming Languages Proficient	Database Good
JavaScript ExpressJs	ExpressJS ThreeJs WebGL	JavaScript TypeScript C#	MongoDB SQL NoSQL
NodeJS TypeScript HTML	ReactJS AngularJS NestJS		
CSS Bootstrap			
Platform	3D Design	Tools	
intermediate	intermediate	VS Code Intellij IDEAs	
AWS Azure Devops	Blender 3D WebGL Model	Blender	
Serverless	Canvas		

WORK EXPERIENCE (2)

Feb 2023 - Current

Senior Software Developer at FPT Software

Working as Fullstack developer and team lead. Proficient in both Frontend and Backend development.

- Join as Senior Software Developer on February 2023
- Leading a team of 10 developers
- Develop IoT Management system for in-house project (Oil & Gas Industry)
- Training and sharing knowledge with Business Unit
- Develop and maintain multiple web applications for clients
- Document and provide technical support for clients

May 2020 - Feb 2023

Software Engineer at Fromlabs Solution Ltd.

Working as Fullstack developer, specialized in MERN Stacks and proficiency in both Frontend and Backend development. Worked on multiple content management sites and web applications.

- Join as Internship around May 2020
- Started as Fullstack Software Enginner on August 2020
- Develop small management sites for clients, such as: Jaktent Event booking, Restaurant management, etc.
- Kickstart Our3D Space project at September 2021
- Moved to Lead Developer of Metaverse by Fromlabs on April 2022

PROJECTS (5)

In-House project (undisclosed due to NDA)

Feb 2023 - Current



- Developed using MEAN Stacks
- Use Express.JS for backend and communicate with MongoDB Database
- Migration to NestJS for better performance and scalability
- Use AngularJS for frontend and iFrame integration
- Use Socket.IO for real-time rendering between users and server
- Use RabbitMQ for message queue between microservices

- Configure and deploy using Azure DevOps
- Using Docker and Portainer for containerization and management

[Personal Project] Simple R3F Game

https://junmaxwell.github.io/r3f-game/

React Three Fiber Three.JS React.JS JavaScript

- Developed using React Three Fiber
- Use Three.JS for 3D rendering and 3D interaction

[Personal Project] Space invaders

https://junmaxwell.github.io/space-invader-favie/

HTML CSS JavaScript ThreeJS Webpack

- Developed purely in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Use ThreeJS for rendering but only use 2 axies for simplicity
- Use Webpack for bundling and deployment

Metaverse by Fromlabs

Oct 2021 - Feb 2023

hhttps://space.fromlabs.com/rooms/?room=TA-7bce80663a34e9



- Create site using React.JS for UI
- Mix with Three.JS for 3D rendering and 3D interaction
- Express.JS for backend and communicate with MongoDB Database
- Use Socket.IO for real-time rendering between users and server
- Use WebRTC for real-time communication between users
- Blender for 3D modeling and animation
- Apply with multiple other microservices such as: Keycloak, Squidex, etc. to provide a complete solution

Indoor Drone R&D

Nov 2019 - Jun 2020

Al Drone Face Recognition Python OpenCV

- Face recognition
- Automated flight

EDUCATION (1)

Bachelor Computer & Information Science at Auckland University of Technology

2016 - 2020

CERTIFICATES

Udacity - Cloud Developer Nanodegree

Udacity

https://confirm.udacity.com/e/058af020-fb65-11ed-addf-8304bc460e72

LANGUAGES

English

Vietnamse

Fluent

Native Speaker